<row><Question>
1. This band contributed songs to the soundtrack for The Other Side of AIDS, and one song by this band declares, “I guess you’re stuck in the Habitrail” and asks “Whatever happened to DayGlo clothes?” Another song by this band charges, “If you’d accept surrender, give up some more,” while in another the singer says “I’m impressed, what a beautiful chest.” In addition to “Walking After You” and (*) “Stacked Actors,” a song by this band admits, “I’ve got another confession to make, I’m your fool,” and another song begins, “Run and tell all the angels this could take all night,” and that song’s chorus says the singer is “Looking for a complication, looking ‘cause I’m tired of trying.” FTP, name this band behind the songs “Best of You” and “Learn to Fly” whose frontman is former Nirvana drummer Dave Grohl.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Foo Fighters </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
2. This man is a Calgary Flames fan who claimed to have had an opportunity to join the NHL, and one episode featuring this character is named after a dictatorial cocoa plantation owner named Trumbo. On another occasion, this character teams up with his antagonist to rescue a woman named Ashton, and that antagonist is a member of Homicide International Trust. This figure was offered a job by (*) Peter Thornton, before going on to work for the Phoenix Foundation. One episode reveals that this man experienced a childhood trauma upon the death of his friend from a falling gun, which is the reason that this character seldom uses a firearm, instead resorting to unconventional methods of capture and escape. FTP, name this resourceful TV hero played by Richard Dean Anderson, who is parodied in SNL sketches in which Will Forte must disarm a ticking bomb with random objects.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Angus Macgyver </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
3. He’s not Michael McShane, but this man voiced Professor Keenbean in the film Richie Rich’s Christmas Wish, and this man talked about subliminal messages in rock ‘n’ roll when he had a cameo as himself in Josie and the Pussycats. In one early appearance, this actor played a victim of the Reverend Alex St. John and his three titular women in Cannibal Girls, and this actor also plays a character who literally has two left feet. That role was as Gerry Fleck, a man who sings about the titular animal’s “cute little derriere” in the song “God Loves a (*) Terrier” in the film Best in Show. This man costarred with Samuel L. Jackson in the buddy cop comedy The Man, but his most notable role is probably that of a man who awkwardly explains to his son about masturbation in one film in a series whose entries include The Naked Mile, Beta House, and Band Camp. FTP, name this Canadian-Jewish comedian who stars as Noah Levenstein in the American Pie series.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Eugene Levy </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
4. The first man to win a national championship while holding this title later coached Duke’s football team, and the stadium is named after him. In addition to Wallace Wade, another man who won a national title at this school had played at Notre Dame with Knute Rockne, and while holding this position coached this position’s most famous holder. Frank (*) Thomas held this position in the 1930s, while a more recent man to take this job won just 13 SEC games in four seasons, or one fewer than his father won at the helm of the 1972 Dolphins. Mike Shula gave way to interim coach Joe Klines before another man took this position and guided the 2009 squad to 6 wins over AP Top 25 Teams en route to a title. Most famously held by Bear Bryant, FTP, name this position currently held by Nick Saban.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Head Coach of Alabama </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
5. This song’s chorus includes a line from another song that itself asks, “so won’t you say you love me? I’ll make you so proud of me,” and that line is delivered by one of that song’s original singers. This song itself begins, “I feel a hunger, and it’s a hunger that tries to keep a man awake at night,” before noting that “anticipation is running through me” and suggests, “let’s find the key and turn this engine on.” The singer asks for “a (*) guardian angel to keep me warm when the cold winds blow,” and this song’s chorus paraphrases the title command with a line that is delivered “just like Ronnie sang.” FTP, name this song whose chorus also asserts “I don’t want to let you go ‘til you see the light,” and asks the listener to “be my little baby” after issuing the title command, by Eddie Money.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> “Take Me Home Tonight” </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
6. One precursor to this event was the Outbound Flight project, whose failure was engineered by the perpetrator of this event, and an unintentional victim of this event was named Boga. One figure who was dismayed by the particular timing of this event was Commander Cody, and lesser known survivors of this event included Rahm Kota and Quinlan Vos, though a more notable survivor was dismayed after viewing a recording of the participation in this event by the (*) 501st Legion. One notable victim of this event was killed shortly after the death of Kit Fisto, after that man’s hand was cut off by one major perpetrator of this event, allowing that man to be hurled to his death. That perpetrator would later lead a massacre of the younglings during this event, before confronting his former master on the lava planet Mustafar. FTP, name this event, initiated by the issuance of Order 66 and orchestrated by Emperor Palpatine, which resulted in the deaths of many of the companions of Yoda and Obi-Wan Kenobi.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Great Jedi Purge (accept anything involving the killing or extermination of the Jedi; accept Order 66 before mentioned) </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
7. In an early television appearance, this man quotes Of Mice and Men and notes “I was just petting it, just petting it George” while attempting to sell a porcelain doll holding a mouse in a stocking, and later he burns his hand on a lava lamp while trying to sell it, causing him to exclaim “Medic!”  This man’s earlier television appearances on QVC were made considerably less boring by his background in singing opera music, and this man recently appeared in a commercial where a woman claims (*) “Looking good!” after this man notes that “My girlfriend says they make my butt look good.”  In addition to that ad for Lee Jeans, this man also appeared in commercials for Epic Pharmacy, and in the show for which this man is most famous, he partakes in occupations such as sucking semen out of chickens, window washing, and birthing cows.  For ten points, name this host of Discovery Channel’s Dirty Jobs.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Mike Rowe </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
8. One version of this film saw one character as a former member of the Nation of Islam who did not “see eye to eye with them over some things,” and at the end of this film, one man introduces himself as “McCardle.” One version of this film sees a James Gandolfini character threaten a character who had bullied an old man, and a (*) baseball game that is continually referred to in this movie is eventually rained out. One character in this film buys a knife with a distinctive handle to prove a point, and that character, an architect named Davis, clashes with another man portrayed by Lee Cobb. This film begins with Henry Fonda’s character casting the only “Nay” vote. FTP, name this 1957 film that sees a jury argue over the guilt of an accused murderer. </row></Question>
<ANSWER:> 12 Angry Men </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
9. Team and year required. Along with the RunTMC Warriors, this is one of two legacy teams that were only available via limited codes distributed by EA for NBA 2k12. In FreeDarko’s Undisputed Guide to Pro Basketball History, Tom Ziller credited this team’s GM of assembling, “a murderous attack it’s not clear even he understood” in the leadup to the lockout, laying the groundwork for this squad.  The awesomely-named Lawrence Funderburke got into more games than rookie Gerald Wallace for this squad, and this team’s second-year players included Mateen Cleaves and Hedo Turkoglu. A midseason trade by (*) Geoff Petrie with the Grizzlies saw this team trade its point guard, Jason Williams, for a former University of Arizona star.  A shot by Samaki Walker in Game 4 of the Western Conference Finals against this squad motivated the NBA to institute instant replay review.  Knocked out of the playoffs by the archrival Lakers in a series Tim Donaghy alleged was fixed, FTP, name this squad that saw the pinnacle of the Divac-Stojakovic-Bibby-Webber tetrarchy.</row></Question>
ANSWER 2002 Sacramento Kings
<row><Question>
10. A real-life version of this object was designed in three weeks by George Barris, and in one instance a character remarks that this object’s name is “totally queer” despite the fact that in another story that character is said to have suggested the name. Another iteration of this object was designed for use specifically by Jean-Paul Valley, and a related object to this one is used by Tim (*) Drake and is called the Redbird. This object was recently upgraded with the help of its user’s son Damian, who retooled it to grant it the capability of flight. This object features a communications system that at one point allows its user contact with Oracle, and it also contains a police radio that allows its owner to remain in touch with Jim Gordon. FTP, name this souped-up car driven by Gotham’s Caped Crusader. </row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Batmobile </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
11. One character on this show has a newsletter proclaiming that if he had his druthers, “Sharon Gless would be on TV every night” and there’d be no world hunger, and at a party on this show, one character continually demands that the main character drink a salty dog. One minor character on this show is Paula, who is portrayed by Janeane (*) Garofalo.  The main character of this show divorces his wife Jeannie in the second season. Another episode sees one character abandon the catchphrase "Hey Now," the Jeffrey Tambor-portrayed Hank Kingsley, and the main character uses the catchphrase “No flipping!” Rip Torn plays the stage manager Artie on this show. FTP, name this HBO show about a fictional late night host portrayed by Garry Shandling.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> The Larry Sanders Show </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
12. One song that mentions this corporation includes the lines, “She’ll wash her hair, his dirty clothes are all he gives to her,” and later claims that “she’s just dressed to kill.” Another song that mentions one of this company’s eponymous products mentions it after asserting “but you always steal the show, and just like that, girl you got me froze.” Far East Movement references one product created by this company in their song “Rocketeer” after asserting “we’re onto next (*) level,” and yet another song asserts that “you don’t get another chance” before declaring that “life is no” product created by this company; that song is “Love the Way You Lie.” This company’s own musical works have been composed in part by Koji Kondo, who has created pieces such as “Gerudo Valley” and “Saria’s Song.” FTP, name this corporation whose own best-known musical work may be the theme to Super Mario Bros.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Nintendo </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
13. The distinctive paint job of Braniff Airways’ 747s led them to be referred to by the name of this figure, who in a Robot Chicken episode goes on a destructive rampage before being eaten by a tree. In a TV episode named in part for this figure, one character worries about being accused of “taking part in a rumble,” while another character offers a third a signed note as a token of her honesty, only to renege on their agreement because it wasn’t notarized. Objects that have been mistaken for this figure include a (*) “bird hippie,” a bowling ball, and someone driving a zamboni, and the character most associated with this figure has insisted that this figure will appear because he “respects sincerity,” and suggests that he will stop believing in this figure when another character stops believing in Santa Claus. Featured in the title of a TV special in which another character repeatedly receives rocks while trick-or-treating, FTP name this mythical gourdfor whom Linus van Pelt waits annually on Halloween night.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> The Great Pumpkin </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
14. In a career that spanned 19 years, she won nine Grand Slam tournaments, though she never captured a Wimbledon title. Winning her first Grand Slam at the age of 16, she became known for a series of matches against Stefi (*) Graf, whom she overtook in 1991 to become the highest ranked female player in the world. Her loud grunting on the court became her trademark, though it elicited complaints from rivals such as Martina Navratilova. After a two-year hiatus, she returned to professional tennis in 1995, and ultimately won a bronze medal for the United States in the 2000 Olympics, six years after becoming a US citizen. FTP, name this tennis player born in Yugoslavia, possibly most famous for a 1993 incident in which a deranged fan stabbed her in the back.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Monica Seles </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
15. On a date in this film, one character asks how long a separation must be required to kiss at a kissing post, and that character’s date becomes distraught upon seeing the signature of her ancestor, the Butcher of Cadiz; this occurs on a date at Ellis Island. That woman relates a story of how her sister Maria almost died after falling into a frozen pond after another scene in this film in which the protagonist experiences an (*) allergic reaction at a food rave and must rush to a drugstore for Benadryl. Characters in this film include the celebrity Allegra Cole, who is courted by Albert Brennaman as he is taught by the protagonist the 90-10 rule of kissing.  Sara Melas breaks up with this film’s protagonist after she finds out his job, though they reunite and the protagonist realizes that all he did was give confidence to his clients. FTP, name this film in which Will Smith plays “date doctor” Alex Hitchens. </row></Question>
<ANSWER:> “Hitch” </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
16. One character played by this actress is revealed to have attended high school with Ray Barone, and this actress assured two characters that eventually, everybody wants her advice in a cameo on an episode of What I Like About You. On another show, this actress played a character who dated a man played by Ryan McPartlin, Riley, and who is the mother of Allison and Josh Reeves. That show was titled (*) Living With this actress’s character, while in this actress’s most famous show her character was pitted against C.C. Babcock and eventually married her employer Maxwell, while she mentored that man’s children Margaret, Grace, and Brighton Sheffield. FTP, name this nasally-voiced actress who a played a character with her real first name on The Nanny. </row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Fran Drescher </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
17. This species lends its name the Polar Bear Dog companion of the protagonist Korra in Korra’s eponymous sequel to Avatar: The Last Airbender. One figure who studied these creatures was Explorers’ League member Hugh Deepstone, notable members of this race include Lady Vashj, and they are ruled over by the Empress Azshara. Members of this race assisted in the recovery of the Eye of (*) Sargeras as part of their alliance with Illidan Stormrage, and fought against the Scourge alongside the blood elves, who are their distant cousins as this race were originally Night Elves before the sundering of the Well of Eternity caused this race to flee and live for thousands of years beneath the ocean. FTP, identify this serpentine race found in the Warcraft franchise named after snake-human hybrids from Hindu myth.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Naga </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
18. One band from this country claims, “That used to be my favorite song,” in “Bittersweet,” a song by this country’s Hoodoo Gurus. One group from this country saw minor hits with the songs “Reptile” and “Metropolis,” although their biggest hit came off their album Starfish. In addition to the band behind “Under the Milky Way,” another group from this country claimed “there’ll be pay in your pocket tonight” if they worked at the title location (*) in “Blue Sky Mine.” That group also performed “Beds Are Burning.” Along with The Church and Midnight Oil, one group from this country had a hit with “New Sensation,” INXS. For ten points, name this country that produced Men at Work, the band behind “Down Under.”</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Australia </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
19. Two of the three cases that prompted the introduction of this system involved players eventually signed by the Yankees, as one player involved in a dispute leading to the creation of this refused to negotiate with the Padres. So far, eleven players have utilized this system as a means of joining an MLB team, though it does not apply to free agents from the league for which it was drafted. The highest dollar amount paid through this system went to the (*) Seibu Lions from the Red Sox, though it may be broken if the Rangers bid for a Nippon Ham Fighters pitcher goes through this week. Governing the transfer of contract-bound players from the Japanese league to MLB, FTP, name this system that sees teams bid for Japanese stars like Daisuke Matsuzaka and Yu Darvish.</row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Posting Fee </ANSWER>
<row><Question>
20. An argument between two characters in this film sees one argue, “If opera goes away, we’re fucked!” and another character in this film displays his certificate of adoption of a dolphin named Simon. Another incident in this movie sees the protagonist don an Annie wig before drugging Carl Halabi and taking blackmail photos of him in compromising poses. A song performed by yet another character in this movie is entitled (*) “Simpatico” and is addressed to that figure’s love interest, who attempts to expose this film’s protagonist after being tricked into eating a poison ivy-covered apple. That victim is the love interest of Scott Delacorte, Amy Squirrel, who is restrained by police in this film after trying to reveal that the protagonist stole a copy of an end-of-the-year exam to increase her students’ test scores. FTP, name this film that features Cameron Diaz as the titular subpar pedagogue. </row></Question>
<ANSWER:> Bad Teacher </ANSWER>
